+91 87927 53090 | nagendra.prajwal@outlook.com | LinkedIn | Bangalore, KA, IN - 560 043

## About me

Having around 10+ years of experience in web development, I have hands-on experience on various technologies like Angular, Nx, React, NextJS, and Flutter. My focus is on *cleaner*, *easy-to-use interfaces* which makes our user's journey a happy one.

# **Work Experience**

### PRINCIPAL SOFTWARE ENGINEER; F5, INC; BANGALORE, INDIA - 2024-PRESENT

Working on F5XC foundation team. Majorly focused on experience (DX) improvements and stability of the platform.

## SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER; F5, INC; BANGALORE, INDIA - 2022-2024

Worked on F5XC Console platform, SaaS features, developer experience (DX) improvements, and stability of the platform.

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER III; F5, INC; BANGALORE, INDIA – 2020-2022**

Worked on F5XC Console platform, brand websites, multiple documentation portals.

#### SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER; VOTERCIRCLE, INC.; BANGALORE, INDIA - 2019-2020

Worked on developing OutreachCircle platform, which is an entirely new, research-based approach of connecting with voters by utilising the supporter's personal contact book. Tech stack used: Angular, React, Flutter, NextJS for various apps along with GraqhQL.

### SENIOR SYSTEMS ENGINEER; INFOSYS LTD.; BANGALORE, INDIA - 2018-2019

Worked on setting up frontend app for CPQ solution of an Agro-Tech company, which has to be used by dealers, customers, and guest users on desktop-web, mobile-web, and mobile-app. Tech stack used: Angular, React, .net Core, and related SAP products.

### SYSTEMS ENGINEER; INFOSYS LTD.; BANGALORE, INDIA - 2016-2018

Worked on analytical tool for a leading Aerospace company. Entire presentation layer was re-written using ASP.NET MVC, jQuery, and Bootstrap in the span of 8 months.

## Education

Visvesvaraya Technological University – Bachelor of Engineering, 2015

# Top Skills

TypeScript, JavaScript, React, Angular, CSS3, Sass, Webpack, Nx.

## Certifications and Accreditations

- Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer App Builder, 2017.
  - Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate Web Applications, 2017.
  - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and ASP.NET MVC (exams: 70 480, 70 486).
- AWS Technical Professional (2015 2017), Partner Accreditation Programme.

For more details, please visit https://www.linkedin.com/in/nagendraprajwal